A Guide to the John Barnes Performing Arts Collection, 1890s-1980s
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series VI: Opera, 1920s-1970s
  - Virginia Opera Association programs 1976-1978 (Box-folder 8-24)
  - The Wagner Opera Company, Inc. program 1959 (Box-folder 8-25)
  - The Washington Grand Opera Association programs 1943-1945 (Box-folder 8-26)
  - Wolf Trap Company program 1976 (Box-folder 8-27)
- Series VII: Ballet and Dance, 1930s-1980
  - Alvin Ailey City Center Dance Theater program 1976 (Box-folder 8-28)
  - American Ballet Theatre programs 1944, 1952, 1973, n.d. (Box-folder 8-29)
  - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo programs and advertisements 1936, 1957, n.d. (Box-folder 8-30)
  - Bat-Dor Dance Company of Israel advertisement After 1968 (Box-folder 8-31)
  - The Bolshoi Ballet program and advertisements 1959, 1967, n.d. (Box-folder 8-32)
  - The Boston Ballet program 1980 (Box-folder 8-33)
  - Charlottesville Civic Ballet Company program n.d. (Box-folder 8-34)
  - City Center Joffrey Ballet program 1975 (Box-folder 8-35)
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem advertisement 1974 (Box-folder 8-36)
  - Fairfax Ballet Company, Inc. program 1971 (Box-folder 8-37)
  - The Grand Theatre and Polish National Opera program 1969 (Box-folder 8-38)
  - Harkness Ballet program 1975 (Box-folder 8-39)
  - Hartford Ballet program 1976 (Box-folder 8-40)
  - Les Ballets Africains program 1959 (Box-folder 8-41)
  - Les Ballet de Paris program 1958 (Box-folder 8-42)
  - Les Grands Ballets Canadiens program 1966 (Box-folder 8-43)
  - Moiseyev Dance Company program 1958 (Box-folder 8-44)
  - The National Ballet (United States of America) programs 1965-1971 (Box-folder 8-45)
  - National Ballet of Canada programs 1960, 1972, n.d. (Box-folder 8-46)
  - National Opera Theatre (France) program 1962-1963 (Box-folder 8-47)
  - New York City Ballet program 1956 (Box-folder 8-48)
  - Original Ballet Russe program 1940 (Box-folder 8-49)
  - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre program 1977 (Box-folder 8-50)
  - The Royal Ballet (Britain) programs and advertisement 1950s-1970s (Box-folder 8-51)
  - State Order of Lenin Academic Opera and Ballet Theatre program 1962 (Box-folder 8-52)
  - The Stuttgart Ballet program 1971 (Box-folder 8-53)
  - Ballet and dance individual performer programs 1930s-1960s (Box-folder 8-54)
- Series VIII: Music, 1920s-early 1980s
  - Chicago Musical College Fifty-Night Commencement Exercises program 1925 (Box-folder 8-55)
  - Civic Musical Association of Richmond programs and advertisement 1943-1958 (Box-folder 8-56)
  - The Community Concert Association (Charlottesville, Virginia) programs and advertisement 1930s-1940s (Box-folder 8-57)
  - Mrs. Dorsey's Concert Bureau programs 1943-1946 (Box-folder 8-58)
  - National Symphony Orchestra (United States of America) programs 1929, 1943-1946, 1957, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 8-59)
  - University of Virginia programs 1940s-1970s
    - Glee Club programs 1940s-1970s (Box-folder 8-60)
    - Tuesday Evening Concert Series programs 1940s-1970s (Box-folder 8-61)
    - Artists Series programs 1940s-1970s (Box-folder 8-62)
    - University Orchestra programs 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 8-63)
  - Virginia Tech Union programs 1970s-1980s
    - Chamber Music Series programs 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 8-64)
    - Concert Series programs 1975-1984 (Box-folder 8-65)
  - Large musical ensemble programs 1920s-1980s
    - Ensemble names A-K 1920s-1980s (Box-folder 8-66)
    - Ensemble names L-W 1920s-1980s (Box-folder 8-67)
  - Individual and small ensemble programs 1920s-1980s (Box-folder 8-68)
  - Music festival programs 1940s-1970s (Box-folder 8-69)
  - Music variety show programs 1950s-1970s (Box-folder 8-70)
- Series IX: Motion Pictures and Television, 1920s-1970s
  - Motion picture and television promotional handouts c.1930-c.1970 (Box-folder 8-71)
  - Film festival film notes 1940s-1950s (Box-folder 9-1)
  - Motion picture brochures and study guides 1945-1965, n.d. (Box-folder 9-2)
  - Motion picture catalogs 1960s (Box-folder 9-3)
  - Motion picture programs 1920s-1930s, 1970s (Box-folder 9-4)
  - The British Film Institute 1950s-1960s
    - Newsletters, reports, invitations, and order forms 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 9-5)
    - National Film Theatre programs 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 9-6)
- Series X: Other Genres, 1930s-1970s
  - Entertainment magazines and directories 1930-1976 (Box-folder 9-7)
  - Museum and library brochures and programs 1978-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 9-8)
  - Circus programs 1950s (Box-folder 9-9)
  - Casino de Paris cabaret programs c.1962 (Box-folder 9-10)
  - Dressage (horse dancing) souvenir program c.1970 (Box-folder 9-11)
  - Figure skating programs 1940-1945 (Box-folder 9-12)